毫无理由相信这些具有敌意嘛
There's no reason to believe their intentions are hostile.
为什么总迂腐地认为外星人是坏蛋呢？
Why is it the egghead position that aliens are always benign?
我们对他们不构成威胁
We pose no threat to them.
好比我们兴师动众去东非
It'd be like us going out of our way
消灭蚂蚁山上的微生物
to destroy microbes on an anthill.
有趣的类比
Interesting analogy.
而我们果真消灭蚂蚁山上的几个微生物  你会觉得内疚吗？
How guilty would we feel if we destroyed a few microbes on an anthill?
我希望你是正确的
I hope you're right.
真的
I really do.
但是  我有责任消除美国人民的任何威胁
But my job is to protect American lives from any threat
因此我必定要做最坏的打算
so I am obligated to assume the worst.
是的  我不能不同意
Yes, and I am forced to agree with you.